[VI] -902, 0201... -There's no sign of the Hollows!
[VI] 2
[VI] -The construction will be complete in a few days! -Captain, this is...
[VI] 3
[VI] They're the only ones who can erase the Hollows from existence.
[VI] 4
[VI] I heard that the Hollows are more likely to appear in Karakura.
[VI] 5
[VI] I was wondering if I was the only one who would come here.
[VI] 6
[VI] What a crowd!
[VI] 7
[VI] I can't face them like this.
[VI] 8
[VI] Who are you?
[VI] 9
[VI] Ichigo Kurosaki.
[VI] 10
[VI] I'm the Death God.
[VI] 11
[VI] -Sorry to keep you waiting! -I don't know who you are.
[VI] 12
[VI] -I don't know why you're attacking me. -Kurosaki, be careful.
[VI] 13
[VI] -Your opponent is... -It's a big problem!
[VI] 14
[VI] -It's Megaman! It's Megaman! -Yes, yes!
[VI] 15
[VI] The big selection tournament is about to begin!
[VI] 16
[VI] -You're the Queen City's... -Do you remember me? Ichigo Kurosaki.
[VI] 17
[VI] Everything that's happening now is connected.
[VI] 18
[VI] It's not just a coincidence.
[VI] 19
[VI] -So you know everything. -It's none of your business.
[VI] 20
[VI] I order all captains to prepare for battle.
[VI] 21
[VI] You damn Death Gods.
[VI] 22
[VI] I, Sternbitter, will purge you.
[VI] 23
[VI] -I understand. I'll go help you. -Let's do this.
[VI] 24
[VI] Bankai!
[VI] 25
[VI] Sorry, but I'm ordering you to kill everyone.
[VI] 26
[VI] -It's none of your business. -I'll beat you up.
[VI] 27
[VI] -Your Bankai ends here! -Please, say something.
[VI] 28
[VI] -Sternbitter! -You have to endure it. Ichigo will come for you.
[VI] 29
[VI] I won't let you die. I won't let you all die.
[VI] 30
[VI] I'll protect you!
[VI] 31
[VI] Sternbitter!
[VI] 32
[VI] Now, let's hear the news of peace.
[VI] 33
[VI] The power to crush fate is like a blade that can be swung down.
[VI] 34
[VI] Sternbitter!
[VI] 35
[VI] Sternbitter